Guide to the Burney Family Collection
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Burney Family Collection Additions, Series II
  - WARTON, JOSEPH, 1722-1800
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1790 Jul 25 (Box 18, Folder 1318)
  - MURPHY, ARTHUR, 1727-1805
    - Letter to Thomas Cadell, 1786 Dec 11 (Box 18, Folder 1319)
  - BARTOLOZZI, FRANCESCO, 1727-1815
    - Receipt for Thomas Lowndes, 1785 Oct 10 (Box 18, Folder 1320)
  - KEATE, GEORGE, 1729-1797
    - Letter to Dr. William Heberden, n.y. Feb 26 (Box 18, Folder 1321)
  - SANDWICH, JOHN MANTAGU, 4TH EARL OF, 1718-1792
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1784 Dec 14 (Box 18, Folder 1322)
  - HARRINGTON, HENRY, 1727-1816
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., [ca. 1807] (Box 18, Folder 1323)
  - DOBSON, SUSANNAH DAWSON
    - Letter to Fanny Burney (Box 18, Folder 1324)
    - Letter to Fanny Burney, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 1325)
  - BURNEY, CHARLES, MUS. D., 1726-1814
    - Letter to Thomas Lowndes, 1779 Jan 27 (Box 18, Folder 1326)
  - BURNEY, CHARLOTTE
    - Letter to Rosette Burney, [1783] Aug 15 (Box 18, Folder 1327)
  - CHAMIER, ANTHONY, 1725-1780
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., n.y. Jun 29 (Box 18, Folder 1328)
  - PIOZZI, HESTER LYNCH (SALUSBURY) THRALE, 1743-1821
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., [1781 Nov] (Box 18, Folder 1329)
  - SACCHINI, ANTONIO, 1730-1786
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., [177?] Jun 9 (Box 18, Folder 1330)
  - ARBLAY, FRANCES BURNEY D', 1752-1840
    - Letter (in third person) to Thomas Lowndes, 1782 Sep 16 (Box 18, Folder 1331)
  - WRAXALL, NATHANIEL WILLIAM, SIR, 1751-1831
    - Letter to Edward Foss, 1805 Apr 4 (Box 18, Folder 1332)
    - Letter to Edward Foss, [1805?] Mar 4 (Box 18, Folder 1333)
  - RAUZZINI, VENANZIO, 1746-1810
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., n.d. (Box 18, Folder 1334)
  - BURNEY, EDWARD FRANCESCO, 1760-1848
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1821 Jan 26 (Box 18, Folder 1335)
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1840 Jun 10 (Box 18, Folder 1336)
  - SIDDONS, SARAH, 1755-1831
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1821 Dec 10 (Box 18, Folder 1337)
  - LUCAN, MARGARET (SMITH) BINGHAM, COUNTESS OF
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., n.d. (Box 18, Folder 1338)
  - WEST, BENJAMIN, 1738-1820
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1803 Dec 29 (Box 18, Folder 1339)
  - NOLLEKENS, JOSEPH, 1737-1823
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1804 Jul 21 (Box 18, Folder 1340)
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1808 Oct 19 (Box 18, Folder 1341)
  - PARR, SAMUEL, 1747-1825
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Jr., n.y. May 6 (Box 18, Folder 1342)
  - JACKSON, WILLIAM, 1730-1803
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1787 Oct 15 (Box 18, Folder 1343)
  - CAMBRIDGE, GEORGE OWEN, 1755 0r 6-1841
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1803 Aug 8 (Box 19, Folder 1344)
  - WARTON, THOMAS, 1728-1790
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1789 Feb 1 (Box 19, Folder 1345)
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1789 Apr 6 (Box 19, Folder 1346)
  - NORTH, BROWNLOW, 1741-1820
    - Letter to [Charles Burney, D.D.], n.y. Mar 31 (Box 19, Folder 1347)
  - DELANY, MARY GRANVILLE PENDARVES, 1700-1788
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., [1785?] Nov 7 (Box 19, Folder 1348)
  - CAMBRIDGE, RICHARD OWEN, 1717-1802
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., n.y. Sep 15 (Box 19, Folder 1349)
  - PHILLIPS, SUSANNAH (ELIZABETH) BURNEY, 1755-1800
    - Letter to Rosette Burney and Charles Burney, D.D., 1783 Jun 24 (Box 19, Folder 1350)
    - Letter to Rosette Burney, [1783] Jul 24 (Box 19, Folder 1351)
  - BERQUIN, M. ARNAUD, 1747-1791
    - Letter to Charlotte Burney, [ca. 1783] (Box 19, Folder 1352)
  - HOOLE, SAMUEL, 1757 OR 8-1839
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1800 Apr 25 (Box 19, Folder 1353)
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1801 May 30 (Box 19, Folder 1354)
  - JOHNSON, SAMUEL, 1709-1784
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1783 Sep 20 (Box 19, Folder 1355)
  - HOOLE, JOHN, 1727-1803
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., n.d. Aug 15 (Box 19, Folder 1356)
  - JERNINGHAM, EDWARD, 1737-1812
    - Letter to Mrs. Mary Robinson, [1793?] (Box 19, Folder 1357)
  - JOHNSON, SAMUEL, 1709-1784
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1784 Nov 17 (Box 19, Folder 1358)
  - SANDBY, PAUL, 1731-1809
    - Signed verses sent to John Hayes, [1785?] (Box 19, Folder 1359)
  - ELIZABETH, PRINCESS OF ENGLAND, 1770-1840
    - Letter to Lady Harrington, [1805?] (Box 19, Folder 1360)
  - TWINING, THOMAS, 1735-1804
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1803 May 9 (Box 19, Folder 1361)
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1792 Sep 3 (Box 19, Folder 1362)
  - MATTHIAS, T. J.
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1807 Jun 22 (Box 19, Folder 1363)
  - PHILLIPS, SUSANNAH (ELIZABETH) BURNEY, 1755-1800
    - Letter to Rosette Burney, [1790] Apr 26 (Box 19, Folder 1364)
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., [1790] Apr 29? (Box 19, Folder 1365)
  - POLIGNAC, [JULES, DUC DE?]
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1763 Oct 15 (Box 19, Folder 1366)
  - GEORGE IV, KING OF GREAT BRITAIN, 1762-1830
    - Letter to the Earl of Holderness, 1774 Jun 30 (Box 19, Folder 1367)
      Letter signed: "George P. of Wales."
  - [SAVOIE-CARIGNAN?], PRINCE DE
    - Letter to [Joly de Fleury?], 1782 Jan 26 (Box 19, Folder 1368)
  - HASTINGS, WARREN, 1732-1818
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1798 Jul 5 (Box 19, Folder 1369)
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1798 Jul 10 (Box 19, Folder 1370)
  - WINDHAM, WILLIAM, 1750-1810
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1791 Sep 5 (Box 19, Folder 1371)
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1805 Jul 5 (Box 19, Folder 1372)
  - FRANCIS, PHILIP, SIR, 1740-1818
    - Letter to William Harwood, 1778 May 27 (Box 19, Folder 1373)
    - Letter to William Harwood, 1777 Jul 15 (Box 19, Folder 1374)
  - FRANCIS, CLEMENT AND CHARLOTTE
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1788 Feb 28 (Box 19, Folder 1375)
  - BURNEY, JAMES, 1750-1821
    - Letter to [Sarah Harriet Burney], n.d. (Box 19, Folder 1376)
  - ROSE, SAMUEL, 1767-1804
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, n.y. Mar 20 (Box 19, Folder 1377)
    - Letter to Rosette Burney, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 1378)
  - FOX, CHARLES JAMES, 1749-1806
    - Letter to Francis Dawson, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 1379)
  - BANKS, SIR JOSEPH, BART., 1743-1820
    - Letter to "My dear sir", 1811 Oct 29 (Box 19, Folder 1380)
  - HANBURY-WILLIAMS, CHARLES, SIR, 1708-1759
    - Letter to George Selwyn, 1745 Oct 8 (Box 19, Folder 1381)
  - BURNEY, RICHARD, 1790-1845
    - Letter to Rosette Burney, 1790 Apr 10 (Box 19, Folder 1382)
  - MASKELYNE, NEVIL, 1732-1811
    - Letter to John Nourse, 1775 Jul 22 (Box 19, Folder 1383)
    - Letter to [a Burney?], 1809 Jun 30 (Box 19, Folder 1384)
  - HEBERDEN, WILLIAM, 1767-1845
    - Letter to Edward Foss, 1825 Jan 2 (Box 19, Folder 1385)
    - Letter to [Charles Burney, D.D.?], n.y. Jan 31 (Box 19, Folder 1386)
  - MOORE, JOHN, ABP. OF CANTERBURY
    - Letter to Charles Burney, 1791 May 24 (Box 19, Folder 1387)
  - SMELT, LEONARD, 1719-1800
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1774 May 23 (Box 19, Folder 1388)
  - PITT, WILLIAM, 1759-1806
    - Letter to unidentified recipient, 1800 May 12 (Box 19, Folder 1389)
  - SMELT, JESSIE
    - Letter to Fanny Burney, 1789 Jan (Box 19, Folder 1390)
    - Letter to Fanny Burney, 1789 Jul 29 (Box 19, Folder 1391)
  - SCHWELLENBERG, MRS.
    - Letter to Fanny Burney, n.y. Sep 15 (Box 19, Folder 1392)
  - WILLIAM IV, KING OF GREAT BRITAIN, 1765-1837
    - Letter to Lord Holderness, 1774 Jul 22 (Box 19, Folder 1393)
      Letter signed: "Guillaume."
  - CHESTERFIELD, PHILIP STANHOPE, EARL OF, 1755-1815
    - Admission ticket for the Antient Consort for Charles Burney, 1801 (Box 20, Folder 1394)
  - COLMAN, GEORGE, 1732-1794
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1787 Aug (Box 20, Folder 1395)
  - DUNCAN, MARY, LADY
    - Letter to Fanny Burney, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 1396)
  - COURTENAY, JOHN, 1741-1816
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., n.y. Sep 20 (Box 20, Folder 1397)
  - PERCY, THOMAS, BP. OF DROMORE, 1729-1811
    - Letter to [J. B. Nichols?], n.d. (Box 20, Folder 1398)
  - [BISHOP OF ST. POL DE LEON]
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1793 Dec 27 (Box 20, Folder 1399)
  - ROBERTSON, WILLIAM, 1721-1793
    - Letter to [William Rose?], 1770 Jun 26 (Box 20, Folder 1400)
  - GILLIES, JOHN, 1747-1836
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1825 Nov 20 (Box 20, Folder 1401)
  - GARRICK, EVA MARIE
    - Letter to "Dr. Burney or Miss Burney", [1783?] (Box 20, Folder 1402)
  - MANSFIELD, DAVID MURRAY, EARL OF, 1727-1796
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1789 Oct 9 (Box 20, Folder 1403)
      Letter signed: "Stormont."
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1789 Nov 4 (Box 20, Folder 1404)
  - ERSKINE, THOMAS, 1788-1870
    - Letter to Samuel Taylor Coleridge, 1841 Feb 23 (Box 20, Folder 1405)
  - YOUNG, ARTHUR, 1741-1820
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1792 Aug 13 (Box 20, Folder 1406)
    - Letter to Charlotte Ann (Burney) Frances Broome, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 1407)
    - PORSON, RICHARD, 1759-1808
      - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1796 May 18 (Box 20, Folder 1408)
  - KNIGHT, MISS [ELLIS CORNELIA]
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., n.d. (Box 20, Folder 1409)
  - RAINE, MATTHEW, 1760-1811
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1811 Feb 8 (Box 20, Folder 1410)
  - YOUNG, ARTHUR, 1741-1820
    - Letter to Charlotte Ann (Burney) Frances Broome, 1786 Feb 20 (Box 20, Folder 1411)
  - ARBLAY, ALEXANDRE JEAN-BAPTISTE PIOCHARD
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1802 Nov 23 (Box 20, Folder 1412)
  - NARBONNE, LOUIS DE, 1755-1813
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., n.d. (Box 20, Folder 1413)
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., n.d. (Box 20, Folder 1414)
  - CONDORCET, MARIE LOUISE SOPHIE DE GROUCHY
    [MARQUISE DE, 1764-1822]
    - Letter to "Citoyen Barbier", [post 1794] (Box 20, Folder 1415)
  - MARMONTEL, JEAN FRANÇOIS, 1723-1799
    - Letter to Voltaire, 1771 Dec 27 (Box 20, Folder 1416)
      Decscribing the death of Helvetius.
  - STAEL, MADAME (ANNE LOUISE GERMAINE) DE, 1766-1817
    - Letter to unidentified recipient, n.y. Dec 26 (Box 20, Folder 1417)
  - NARBONNE, LOUIS DE, 1755-1813
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., n.y. Sep 20 (Box 20, Folder 1418)
  - [CUTLER, W.?]
    - Letter to unidentified recipient, n.y. Oct 18 (Box 20, Folder 1419)
  - ARBLAY, FRANCES BURNEY D', 1752-1840
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1793 Jul 23 (Box 20, Folder 1420)
  - BURNEY, CHARLES, D.D., 1757-1817
    - Letter to Fanny Burney, 1793 Jul (Box 20, Folder 1421)
  - ADOLPHUS FREDERICK, DUKE OF CAMBRIDGE, 1774-1850
    - Letter to William Skelton, 1810 Dec 18 (Box 20, Folder 1422)
    - Letter to an officer of the Society of Schoolmasters, 1830 Oct 23 (Box 20, Folder 1423)
    - Letter to "Dear Sir", 1811 Apr 3 (Box 20, Folder 1424)
  - SMITH, CHARLOTTE TURNER, 1749-1806
    - Letter to George G. Robinson, 1792 Jul 4 (Box 20, Folder 1425)
  - CREWE, FRANCES ANNE (GREVILLE), 1748-1818
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., [1792?] (Box 20, Folder 1426)
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., n.d. (Box 20, Folder 1427)
  - CANNING, GEORGE, 1770-1827
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1807 Jun 23 (Box 20, Folder 1428)
  - KEMBLE, JOHN PHILIP, 1757-1823
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., [1798] (Box 20, Folder 1429)
  - NARES, ROBERT, 1753-1829
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1804 Jun 13 (Box 20, Folder 1430)
  - ARBLAY, FANNY BURNEY D', 1752-1840
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1796 Jun 17 (Box 20, Folder 1431)
  - CLÉRY, M., 1759-1809
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1798 Jun 2 (Box 20, Folder 1432)
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1798 Jun 16 (Box 20, Folder 1433)
  - YOUNG, JOHN, CA. 1750-1820
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1798 May 9 (Box 20, Folder 1434)
    - Letter to Edward Foss, 1818 Nov 30 (Box 20, Folder 1435)
  - ROTHES, COUNTESS OF
    - Letter to Frederica A. S. Locke, 1797 Nov 19 (Box 20, Folder 1436)
  - ARBLAY, FANNY BURNEY D', 1752-1840
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1800 Nov 18 (Box 20, Folder 1437)
  - BERTHIER, LOUIS-ALEXANDRE, 1753-1815
    - Payment order to Admiral Gauteaume, 1798 Dec 12 (Box 20, Folder 1438)
  - ARBLAY, FANNY BURNEY D', 1752-1840
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1802 Mar 24 (Box 20, Folder 1439)
  - DAMER, ANNE
    - Letter to unidentified recipient, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 1440)
  - LOUIS BONAPARTE, KING OF HOLLAND, 1778-1846
    - Orders to Admiral Marié Marsaine, 1802 Dec 15 (Box 20, Folder 1441)
  - CAMBACÉRES, ETIENNE HUBERT
    [CARDINAL, 1756-1818]
    - Letter to unidentified recipient, 1816 Dec 18 (Box 20, Folder 1442)
  - WHITWORTH, CHARLES WHITWORTH, EARL, 1752-1825
    - Letter to Fanny Burney, 1803 Jan 22 (Box 20, Folder 1443)
  - ARBLAY, ALEXANDRE JEAN-BAPTISTE PIOCHARD
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1812 Jul 20 (Box 21, Folder 1444)
  - PROCURATION FOR FANNY BURNEY
    - Power of attorney allowing Fanny Burney to act "at her own discretion" with regard to her property, signed by Fanny Burney d"Arblay and Alexandre d'Arblay., 1812 Jul 3 (Box 21, Folder 1445)
  - MILMAN, FRANCIS, SIR, 1746-1821
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1813 May 4 (Box 21, Folder 1446)
  - CREWE, BARON
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., n.d. (Box 21, Folder 1447)
  - DAVY, MARTIN, 1763-1839
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1833 Nov 9 (Box 21, Folder 1448)
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1807 Jul 1 (Box 21, Folder 1449)
  - BERRY, MARY, 1763-1852
    - Letter to Edward Foss, n.y. Jan 7 (Box 21, Folder 1450)
  - BURNEY, SARAH HARRIET, 1772-1844
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1813 Dec 8 (Box 21, Folder 1451)
  - BURNEY, CHARLES, MUS.D., 1726-1814
    - Letter to Sarah Harriet Burney, 1813 Aug 19 (Box 21, Folder 1452)
  - WILBERFORCE, WILLIAM, 1759-1833
    - Letter to [Charles Burney, D.D.?], n.d. (Box 21, Folder 1453)
    - Letter to Edward Elliott, 1819 Aug 10 (Box 21, Folder 1454)
  - ROSE, HARRIET
    - Letter to Rosette (Rose) Burney, 1814 Apr 23 (Box 21, Folder 1455)
  - GRATTAN, HENRY, 1746-1820
    - Note to Samuel Parr, 1818 Sep 15 (Box 21, Folder 1456)
  - LA CHATRE, COMTE DE
    - Letter to Amelia Angerstein, 1814 Apr 22 (Box 21, Folder 1457)
  - SERENT, DUCHESSE DE
    - Letter to Fanny Burney, 1815 Feb 22 (Box 21, Folder 1458)
  - -----, BERTRAND
    - Letter to unidentified recipient, 1815 May 12 (Box 21, Folder 1459)
  - UNIDENTIFIED
    - Letter to "coussine", n.d. (Box 21, Folder 1460)
  - JOSEPHINE, EMPRESS, CONSORT OF NAPOLEON I
    [EMPEROR OF THE FRENCH, 1763-1814]
    - Letter to "mon amiable Général", 1801 May-Jun (Box 21, Folder 1461)
      Letter signed: "Lapagerie Bonaparte."
  - LOUIS PHILIPPE, KING OF THE FRENCH, 1773-1850
    - Letter to Mr. Kelly of the Society of Distressed Schoolmasters, 1816 Dec 10 (Box 21, Folder 1462)
      Letter signed: "Orleans."
  - HOLROYD, [SARAH MARTHA?]
    - Letter to Fanny Burney, 1816 Jun 7 (Box 21, Folder 1463)
  - BOWDLER, H. M. (HENRIETTA MARIA), 1754-1830
    - Letter to Fanny Burney, 1818 Jan 29 (Box 21, Folder 1464)
  - ARBLAY, ALEXANDER CHARLES LEWIS, D'
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1817 Jan 20 (Box 21, Folder 1465)
      In part by Alexandre d'Arblay.
  - BURNEY, ESTHER (BURNEY), 1749-1832
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1806 Jan 8 (Box 21, Folder 1466)
  - EDWARD AUGUSTUS, DUKE OF KENT, 1767-1820
    - Proxy authorization for Charles Burney, D.D. at the election of a surgeon to the Kent Dispensary, 1814 Feb 17 (Box 21, Folder 1467)
  - ARBLAY, ALEXANDER CHARLES LEWIS, D'
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1818 Jun 28 (Box 21, Folder 1468)
  - ANDREWES, GERRARD, 1750-1825
    - Letter to Rev. George Lock, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 1469)
  - CASTLEREAGH, ROBERT STEWART, VISCOUNT, 1769-1822
    - Letter to "Lord Stewart", 1820 Jul 4 (Box 21, Folder 1470)
  - ARBLAY, FANNY BURNEY D', 1752-1840
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1827 Jun 26 (Box 21, Folder 1471)
  - SOUTHEY, ROBERT, 1774-1843
    - Letter to [William Locke], n.y. Nov 26 (Box 21, Folder 1472)
  - BURNEY, CHARLES, MUS.D., 1726-1814
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1781 Feb 25 (Box 21, Folder 1473)
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1799 May 22 (Box 21, Folder 1474)
      Letter signed: "C.B. Nicodemus."
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., [1801?] Nov 27 (Box 21, Folder 1475)
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1802 Feb 17 (Box 21, Folder 1476)
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1802 Dec 28 (Box 21, Folder 1477)
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1806 Apr 19 (Box 21, Folder 1478)
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1806 Apr 23 (Box 21, Folder 1479)
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1808 Jun 24 (Box 21, Folder 1480)
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1808 Oct 25 (Box 21, Folder 1481)
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1809 Jun 28 (Box 21, Folder 1482)
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1809 Jul 1 (Box 21, Folder 1483)
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1811 May 16 (Box 21, Folder 1484)
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1812 Jan 6 (Box 21, Folder 1485)
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1812 Jan 10 (Box 21, Folder 1486)
    - Letter to Dr. [Edward] Miller, 1799 Sep 17 (Box 21, Folder 1487)
    - Letter to Mrs. Sheridan, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 1488)
    - Letter to Charlotte Smith, 1793 Aug 19 (Box 22, Folder 1489)
    - Manuscript of musical examples from Josquin des Prez, Pietro Aaron, and Jehan Okenheim (Box 22, Folder 1490)
  - BURNEY, CHARLES, D.D., 1757-1817
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1805 Nov 20 (Box 22, Folder 1491)
      Related Archival Materials note
      See also: Box 6, folder 399
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1806 Mar 22 (Box 22, Folder 1492)
    - Letter (fragment) to Charles Parr Burney, 1806 Nov 3 (Box 22, Folder 1493)
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1806 Nov 22 (Box 22, Folder 1494)
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1807 Jun 5 (Box 22, Folder 1495)
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1808 Jan 4 (Box 22, Folder 1496)
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1808 Jan 14 (Box 22, Folder 1497)
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1808 Jan 15 (Box 22, Folder 1498)
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1808 Jan 18 (Box 22, Folder 1499)
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1808 Jun 22 (Box 22, Folder 1500)
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1808 Jun 4 (Box 22, Folder 1501)
    - Letter to "My dear Boys and Girls", 1801 Jan 18 (Box 22, Folder 1502)
    - Notes in Latin concerning himself, 1791 Jun (Box 22, Folder 1503)
  - BURNEY, SARAH [HARRIET, 1772-1844?]
    - Letter to "My dear sister", n.y. Aug 30 (Box 22, Folder 1504)
  - CURRY, JAMES
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1808 Feb 13 (Box 22, Folder 1505)
  - HEY, JOHN, 1734-1815
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1790 May 20 (Box 22, Folder 1506)
  - MACKNIGHT, THOMAS
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1784 Jun 8 (Box 22, Folder 1507)
  - PHILLIPS, THOMAS, 1770-1845
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1817 jan 5 (Box 22, Folder 1508)
  - PITT, J.
    - Letter to [Esther Sleepe Burney?], 1753 (Box 22, Folder 1509)
  - ROSE, E[LIZABETH]
    - Letter to Rosette Burney, 1797 Nov 8 (Box 22, Folder 1510)
  - WRAXALL, NATHANIEL WILLIAM, SIR, 1751-1831
    - Letter to Edward Foss, 1803 Jul 25 (Box 22, Folder 1511)
  - CARTER, MRS. MARY
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., n.d. (Box 22, Folder 1512)
  - BURNEY, CHARLES, MUS.D., 1726-1814
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1801 Jun 23 (Box 22, Folder 1513)
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1808 Jul 4 (Box 22, Folder 1514)
  - BURNEY, CHARLES, D.D., 1757-1817
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1806 Mar 23 (Box 22, Folder 1515)
  - ARBLAY, M. DE
    - Letter to Alexandre D'Arblay, [1818?] (Box 22, Folder 1516)
  - ROGERS, SAMUEL, 1763-1855
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1807 Jul 6 (Box 22, Folder 1517)
  - UNIDENTIFIED
    - Copy and translation of a Latin passage on the authority of the church (Box 22, Folder 1518)
- Addition of August 2001, Series III
  - BURNEY, CHARLES, MUS.D., 1726-1814
    - ALS to [Susannah Burney], 1789 Apr 30 (Box 23, Folder 1519)
      Accompanied a copy of his History of Music (not present)
    - ALS to [Dr. Samuel Arnold]; Chelsea College, 1801 Jun 27 (Box 23, Folder 1520)
      Concerning relief for the widow of Michael Arne
    - ALS to [Charles Parr Burney], [ca. 1814] (Box 23, Folder 1521)
  - BURNEY, CHARLES PARR, 1785-1864
    - ALS to "dear Mama" [Rosette (Rose) Burney]; Bath, 1796 Jan 21 (Box 23, Folder 1522)
  - UNIDENTIFIED AUTHOR
    - List of toasts for a celebration, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 1523)
      Includes "To the Burneyites in the Church" and "To the B-- in general" Written on letter fragment to "Dear Sir" concerning "Summer "Holidays" schedule
  - BURNEY, CHARLES, D.D., 1757-1817
    - ALS to Charles [Parr Burney]; Caius College, 1807 Jan 8 (Box 23, Folder 1524)
  - LAWRENCE, EDWARD A. (EDWARD ALEXANDER), 1803-1883
    - ALS to Charles Parr Burney; Trinity College, 1832 Jan 20 (Box 23, Folder 1525)
      Concerning examination results for Senior Wrangler
  - CURREY, JAMES
    - ALS to Charles Parr Burney; Benet College, 1808 May 22 (Box 23, Folder 1526)
  - CREWE, JOHN, BARON CREWE
    - DS appointing Charles Parr Burney as his "Domestick Chaplain", 1808 Jan 1 (Box 23, Folder 1527)
      With: wax seal of Baron Crewe Witnessed by F. A. Crewe and Thomas Firminger
  - INDUCTION MANDATE
    - Printed form, completed and signed, confirming the induction of Charles Parr Burney as Rector of Hinton Parva in Salisbury, 1811 Jul 28 (Box 23, Folder 1528)
      Signature and seal of Matthew Raine, Commissary; Attestation by W. H. Hawkins Signed by Edward Lee and Charles Parr Burney
  - BURNEY, CHARLES, D.D., 1757-1817
    - ALS to "Mr. Ross", 1799 Apr 18 (Box 23, Folder 1529)